# Jim Hazlewood

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

416-799-7247
jim.haz34@gmail.com

Portfolio | Linkedin | Github

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5 | CSS3 | Sass | JavaScript

(ES6+) | jQuery | React.js | Firebase |

RESTful APIs | Git & Git Hub |

Responsive UI | Code Review |

Accessibility | Peer Programming |

Mustache.js | Webpack(npm) |

WCAG 2.1 | Nextjs | Typescript

#### **EDUCATION**

Juno College of Technology Web Development Bootcamp,

Accelerated JavaScript Course, Web Development Course

#### CMA, CPA

Chartered Professional Accountants of Ontario

## University of Guelph

Bachelor of Commerce, Marketing

#### **PROFILE**

I'm an intermediate front-end developer skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. I have experience working under tight deadlines, collaborating with teams, and paying close attention to detail. My focus is on creating visually appealing, user-friendly, and accessible websites using best frontend practices.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Q4 Inc.

Web Developer II

Apr 2023 - Present

- Developing exceptional, fully responsive investor relation websites for high-profile clients using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams to deliver layouts, functionality, and user interface interactions for websites, while implementing performance optimization techniques and coding accessible interfaces.

#### Web Developer I

Jan 2022 - Apr 2023

 Built accessible and responsive investor relation websites using HTML5, CSS3, Sass, jQuery, and Q4's Content Management system; troubleshooted and resolved customer support tickets and site bugs using root cause analysis; collaborated with business partners using agile practices.

## Kellogg Canada Inc.

Senior Financial Analyst

Jan 2018 - Aug 2021

#### **SELECTED PROJECTS**

### Taskify

[LIVE] [REPO]

REACT, CSS, FIREBASE

Created an interactive one-page application that allows the user to add, modify, remove or defer tasks. Using Firebase, data is stored and changed.

#### **Digital Cinephile**

[LIVE] [REPO]

HTML, SCSS, JAVASCRIPT, API, PAIR PROGRAMMING

Leveraged MovieDB API to create an app that generates movie and TV recommendations while incorporating JavaScript and error handling.

#### Al Trivia Generator

[LIVE] [REPO]

NEXTIS, TYPESCRIPT, CSS, API,

Leveraging the Openai API, a user can generate a trivia game on any topic with varying difficulty.